Finding Aid of the Society of American Archivists Records, 1935-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1935-2016, UWM Manuscript Collection 172; 271.9 cubic ft. (385 boxes, including 16 audio cassettes and 33 videocassettes) 1 oversize folder 7,545 digital files (26.2 GB) 1 film reel 5 microfilm reels approximately 170 books and serial titles
  - 6. Executive Director, 1959-2005, 200/06
    - 8. Council Files, 1987-2003, 200/06/08; 5.4 cubic ft. (6 boxes)
      - Meetings, 2003 January 10-11 (Box 4, Folder 37-38)
      - Meetings, 2003 May 19-21 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
      - Meetings, 2003 August 23 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Meetings, 2004 February 7-8 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
      - Meetings, 2004 June 4-6 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Meetings, Executive Director Search Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Meetings, Planning Day, 1991 June 13 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Meetings, Planning Day, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Meetings, Planning Day, 1993 July 16-17 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Meetings, Planning Day, 1994 June (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Meetings, Planning Day, 1995 June (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Meetings, Planning Day, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Meetings, Planning Day, 2004 February 5 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 9. SAA Units Files, 200/06/09
      - 1. Boards, 1987-2002, 200/06/09/01; .8 cubic ft. (2 boxes)
        - Editorial Board
          - 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
          - 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
          - 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
          - 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
          - 1996, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
          - Kluwer Proposal, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
          - Reports, 1986-1988, 1990, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - Education Office Advisory Board
          - 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
          - 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
          - Midwinter Meeting, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
          - Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - Publications Management Board
          - 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
          - 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
          - Editor Applicants, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - Leader's Summit, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
          - Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Standards Board, 1991-1997 (Box 2, Folder 5-9)
      - 2. Committees, 1975-2002, 200/06/09/02; 3 cubic ft. (6 boxes)
        - Archival Information Exchange Committee (CAIE)
          - 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
          - 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
          - Reports, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        - Auditing Committee, Reports, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - Automated Records and Techniques Committee (CART)
          - 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
          - 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
          - 1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
          - Meeting, 1993 April 21-22 (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - Reports, 1988-1989, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - Awards Committee
          - 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
          - 1994-2002 (Box 6, Folder 3-5)
          - Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - Committee Codes, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - Committee on Cataloging: Description and Access (CC:DA), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Education and Professional Development Committee (CEPD)
          - 1984-1994 (Box 2, Folder 5-8)
          - 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 7-9)
          - 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
          - Midwinter Meeting, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
          - Reports, 1987-1989, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - Electronic Records Committee, Reports, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        - Ethics and Professional Development Committee
          - 1995-1996, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
          - 1997-2001 (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
        - Goals and Priorities Committee (CGAP)
          - 1985-1993 (Box 3, Folder 1-5)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 15)
          - 2020 Vision, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 16)
          - 2020 Vision, Fundraising, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
          - 2020 Vision, Payments and Contributions, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 18)
          - 2020 Vision, Speaker Contracts, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 19)
          - Analysis of SAA Unit Reports and Plans, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 20)
          - Meeting, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 21)
          - Meeting, 1993 May 3-4 (Box 3, Folder 6)
          - Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
          - Meeting, 1994 February 12-14, 1995 March 9-10, 1995 August 30 (Box 6, Folder 22)
          - Midwinter Meeting, 1996 February 23-25 (Box 6, Folder 23)
          - Reports, 1987-1989, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
          - Strategic Planning, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 24-25)
          - Strategic Planning Survey, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 26)
          - Summer Planning Group, 1993 July (Box 6, Folder 27)
          - Survey of Leadership, 1992 January (Box 6, Folder 28)
        - Host Committee
          - 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
          - 1994-1998, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 29)
          - Reports, 1987, 1989, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
        - Institutional Evaluation and Development Committee (CIED)
          - 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 30)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 31)
          - Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
        - International Archival Affairs Committee
          - 1988-1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
          - 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 32-34)
          - Reports, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        - Legal and Legislative Issues Committee
          - 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
          - 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 35-37)
          - Reports, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        - Local Arrangements Committee
          - 1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
          - 1996 (Box 6, Folder 38)
        - Membership Committee
          - 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
          - 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
          - 1997-2002 (Box 6, Folder 39)
          - Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
        - Nominating Committee
          - 1987-1994 (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
          - 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 40)
          - Reports, 1987, 1989, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
        - Professional Standards Committee
          - 1975-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
          - 2002-2005 (Box 6, Folder 41)
          - Reports, 1989, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        - Program Committee
          - 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
          - 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 42-44)
          - Reports, 1987, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 14)
        - Public Information Committee
          - 1985-1994 (Box 4, Folder 9-10, 12)
          - 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 45-46)
          - Meeting, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
          - Midwinter Meeting, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 47)
          - Reports, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
        - Regional Archival Activity Committee (CRAA)
          - 1987-1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
          - Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
        - Selection of Archival Fellows Committee
          - 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 48)
          - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 49)
        - Standards Committee, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 50)
        - Status of Women Committee
          - 1987-1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
          - 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 51-53)
          - Reports, 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - 3. Representatives, 1985-2002, 200/06/09/03; 2.2 cubic ft. (6 boxes)
        - Academy of Certified Archivists (ACA)
          - 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
          - 1994-1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        - Advisory Committee, United States Department of State Historic Diplomatic Documentation
          - 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
          - 1994-1995, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
        - AASLH/National Information Center for Local Government Records (NICLOG) Advisory Group
          - 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
          - Reports, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - AHA/OAH/SAA Joint Committee of Historians and Archivists
          - 1986-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6-8)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
          - Meeting, 1991 November (Box 1, Folder 9)
          - Meeting, 1992 March (Box 1, Folder 10)
          - Meeting, 1992 October (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 11)
          - Meeting,1992 October (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
          - Meeting, 1993 March (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - Meeting, 1993 October (Box 2, Folder 3)
          - Meeting, 1994 March (Box 2, Folder 4)
          - Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - American Institute for Conservation (AIC)
          - 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
          - 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 8-10)
          - Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - ALA Ad Hoc Task Force on External Accreditation, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
        - ALA Committee on Cataloging
          - 1988-1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
          - Reports, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        - ALA/SAA Joint Committee on Archives and Library Relationships
          - 1987-1994 (Box 2, Folder 11-13)
          - 1994-1995, 1997-1998, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
          - Reports, 1985-1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - Archives and Records Information Coalition (ARIC)
          - 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
          - Reports, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        - Association for Information and Image Management (AIIM)
          - 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
          - Reports, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
        - ARMA/SAA Joint Committee
          - 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
          - 1994-2002 (Box 5, Folder 11-16)
          - Reports, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        - Association of Canadian Archivists, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
        - Association of Research Libraries
          - 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
          - Reports, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - Bureau of Canadian Archives Committee on Descriptive Standards, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
        - Commission on Preservation and Access
          - 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
          - Reports, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - Commission on Soviet - US Archival Cooperation (IREX - International Resources and Exchanges Board)
          - 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
          - Reports, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - Congressional Liaison Working Group, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        - Council on National Library and Information Associations, Inc. (CNLIA)
          - 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
          - Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
        - Descriptive Standards, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
        - Education Office Advisory Board, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        - Historical Documentary Study Advisory Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
        - ICA Committee on Descriptive Standards, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 2)
        - ICA Section of Professional Archival Associations
          - 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
          - 1994-1995, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 3)
          - Reports, 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
        - John F. Kennedy Assassination Records Review Board, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
        - National Afro-American Museum and Cultural Center Planning Commission
          - 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
          - 1994-1995, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 4)
          - Reports, 1989, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
        - NARA Archives II Users Planning Committee
          - 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
          - Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 25)
        - NAGARA, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
        - National Coordinating Committee for the Promotion of History
          - 1987-1994 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
          - 1994-1995, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
          - Reports, 1987, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        - National Historical Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC)
          - 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
          - 1996, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
          - Reports, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        - National Information Standards Organization (NISO)
          - 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
          - 1996, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
          - 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
          - Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
        - National Institute for the Conservation of Cultural Property (NIC)
          - 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
          - 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 8)
          - Reports, 1989, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
        - Network Advisory Committee
          - 1986-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
          - Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
        - Representative Memo of Agreement, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
        - USMARC Advisory Group/ALA
          - 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
          - 1997-2001 (Box 6, Folder 12)
          - Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - 4. Roundtables, 1985-2002, 200/06/09/04; 1.2 cubic ft. (3 boxes)
        - African-American and Third World Archivists Roundtable (ATT-WAR)
          - 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
          - 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
          - Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        - Architectural Records Roundtable
          - 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
          - 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
          - Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - Archival Educators Roundtable
          - 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
          - Reports, 1989, 1991, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        - Archival History Roundtable
          - 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
          - 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
          - Reports, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - Archives Management Roundtable
          - 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
          - 1994-2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
          - Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        - Archivists and Archives of Color, 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - Archivists for Congregations of Women Religious (ACWR), [see Women Religious Archives Roundtable (WRA)]
        - Art and Architecture Thesaurus Roundtable
          - 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
          - 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
          - Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        - Congressional Papers Roundtable
          - 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
          - 1993-2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
          - Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - EAD Roundtable, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - Electronic Records Roundtable
          - 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
          - Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - Gay and Lesbian Archives Roundtable
          - 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
          - 1993-2001 (Box 3, Folder 10)
          - Reports, 1989, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - GEAC Users Roundtable
          - 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
          - Reports, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - International Archival Affairs Roundtable (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - Labor Archives Roundtable
          - 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
          - Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
        - Local Government Records Roundtable
          - 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
          - 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
          - Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
        - MARC-VM (Visual Materials) Users Roundtable
          - 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
          - 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
          - Reports, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
        - MARCON Users Roundtable
          - 1987-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
          - Reports, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - MicroMARC Users Roundtable
          - 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
          - 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
          - Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Minorities Roundtable
          - 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
          - Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - Museum Archives Roundtable [see Museum Archives Section]
        - NOTIS Users Roundtable, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        - OCLC Users Roundtable
          - 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
          - Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - Performing Arts Roundtable
          - 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
          - 1998-2002 (Box 3, Folder 18)
        - Privacy and Confidentiality Roundtable
          - 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
        - Proposed Roundtable Form, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
        - Recorded Sound Roundtable
          - 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
          - 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 21)
          - Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - Records Management Roundtable, 1997-2001 (Box 3, Folder 22)
        - RLIN Users Roundtable
          - 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
          - Reports, 1989, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        - Science, Technology and Healthcare Roundtable
          - 1985-1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
          - 1993-2002 (Box 3, Folder 23)
          - Reports, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
        - Security Roundtable, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 24)
        - Women Archivists Roundtable, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 25)
        - Women Religious Archives Roundtable (WRA)
          - 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
          - 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
          - Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - Women's Collections Roundtable
          - 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 28)
          - Reports, 1990, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - Visual Materials Cataloging and Access Roundtable, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - 5. Sections, 1986-2004, 200/06/09/05; 2 cubic ft. (4 boxes)
        - Acquisitions and Appraisal Section
          - 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
          - 1994-2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
          - Reports, 1987-1989, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        - Archivists of Religious Collections Section [see also Religious Archives Section]
          - 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
          - 1994-2004 (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
          - Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - Aural and Graphic Records Section, Reports, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - Business Archives Section
          - 1986-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
          - 1994-2002 (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
          - Reports, 1987-1990, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        - College and University Archives Section
          - 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
          - 1994-2004 (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
          - Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - Conservation Section
          - 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
          - Reports, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - Description Section
          - 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
          - 1994-2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
          - Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - Electronic Records Section
          - 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
          - 1994-2002 (Box 4, Folder 9)
        - Government Records Section
          - 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - 1994-2004 (Box 4, Folder 10)
          - Reports, 1987-1989, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - Manuscript Repositories Section
          - 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
          - 1994-2004 (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
          - Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - Museum Archives Section
          - 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
          - 1994-2001 (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
          - Reports, 1987-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - Oral History Section
          - 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
          - 1994-2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
          - Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        - Preservation Section
          - 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
          - 1994-2004 (Box 4, Folder 16)
          - Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - Reference, Access, and Outreach Section
          - 1988-1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
          - 1994-2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
          - Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        - Religious Archives Section, 1987-1992 [see also Archivists of Religious Collections Section] (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
        - Section Guidelines
          - 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
          - 1987, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 18)
        - Visual Materials Section
          - 1987-1994 (Box 3, Folder 4-6)
          - 1994-2004 (Box 4, Folder 19-21)
          - Reports, 1988-1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - 6. Task Forces, 1981-2002, 200/06/09/06; 1.6 cubic ft. (3 boxes)
        - Annual Meeting Task Force, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
        - Archival Standards Task Force, Reports, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        - Archives and Society Task Force
          - 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
          - Reports, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        - Automated Records and Techniques Task Force (ART)
          - 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
          - Reports, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        - Automated Techniques Activities Coordination Task Force (ATAC)
          - 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
          - 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
        - Coalitions Task Force, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        - Congressional Liaison Task Force, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - Continuing Education Task Force
          - 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
          - 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
          - Final Report, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - Copyright Task Force
          - 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
          - Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        - Development Task Force, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - Diversity Task Force, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - Dues Increase Task Force, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - Electronic Publishing Task Force, 1999-2002
          - 1999, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
          - Subcommittee Reports, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        - Electronic Records Strategies Task Force, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
        - Ethics Task Force
          - 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
          - Reports, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        - Future of the American Archivist Task Force, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
        - Guidelines for Consulting Archivists Task Force, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - Institutional Evaluation Task Force
          - 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
          - Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - Intellectual Property Strategies Task Force, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        - Library Archives Task Force
          - 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
          - Reports, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - National Information Systems Task Force (NISTF)
          - Original Papers, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
          - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        - Organizational Effectiveness Task Force, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
        - Preservation Task Force
          - 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
          - Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - Records Management Task Force
          - 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
          - Reports, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - SAA Coalitions Task Force, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - Sections and Roundtables Task Force
          - 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 7-9)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
          - Reports, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 7. American Archivist, 1936-2012, 200/07
    This record subgroup consists of records relating to the production of the American Archivist, SAA's journal. The editor's records date from 1936 and anticipate the publication of the first issue in January 1938. Records of the book reviews editor date from 1942, although the American Archivist has devoted sections to announce and review publications relevant to archives administration since its first issue. Records of the advertising editor date from 1948, when the American Archivist first included advertisements among its pages. The bulk of the record subgroup consists of documentation pertaining to the editorial process and includes manuscripts submitted for publication, evaluations of manuscripts by the editorial board, the editors' summaries of board evaluations, editor-author correspondence.